Aleksandr Yanyuk



alex745i@gmail.com





9165791657





https://aleksandr-yanyuk.github.io/Aleksandr-Yanyuk.io/

Summary

I enjoy breaking difficult problems into small tasks to bring clarity to everyday tools. I enjoy being an active team member who uses clear communication and collaboration day to day. I have experience in the following:

Main Languages: C#, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5, TypeScript, SCSS

Databases: Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL, T-SQL, Azure Studio SQL, LINQ, Entity Framework Core

Frameworks: .NET Core, ASP.NET Core MVC, ASP.NET Web APIs, Bootstrap, Angular 13, NgRx, Redux, Jasmine & Karma, Selenium WebDriver, Kendo UI, jQuery

Other: GitHub, JIRA, HTTPS, TCP/IP, Agile/Scrum, AWS, Azure, AWS Lambda, RESTful API, Redux Dev Tools, Postman, Enterprise Code Development, CI/CD: Jenkins, AWSCodeBuild, Microsoft Azure App Services

Experience



Software Engineer/Full Stack Developer

Prosper IT Consulting

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023 (4 months)

I was a part of a live project where we had sprint/stand up/retrospective meetings Monday-Friday. In this team project I created a contact page for the Theatres Website and I also created the MVC/Crude pages for the calendar events. I am always busy improving my skills, working on projects using skills such as .NET Core Web Apps, Crud pages, Razor Rages JavaScript, Html, CSS, SQL, GITHUB, Azure Devops and much more as a C# .NET FullStack Developer.

Software Engineer Freelance

Feb 2022 - Nov 2022 (10 months)

I was working on personal projects, learning how to code, then decided to make a career change and make it official by getting certified for the skills listed in my resume.

Education



The Tech Academy

Software Engineer/Full Stack Developer

2022 - 2023

- Completed the Software Developer Bootcamp with over 800 hours of hands on experience.
- Trained to program/develop in several computing languages such as C#, ASP.NET MVC, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL which are necessary for Full-Stack Development.
- Learned and developed using technologies/frameworks such as, to .NET Framework, Microsoft's Entity Framework, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, jQuery, CSS Bootstrap, Back-End and Front-End web development.

• Learned about and Agile Scrum methodology, Object-Oriented Principles and used version control Git.

Licenses & Certifications



C# .NET - The Tech Academy

Skills

SQL • Azure DevOps • Git • Microsoft Azure • ASP.NET MVC • Entity Framework • .NET Framework • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Microsoft SQL Server